<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sermonstuffs on Seunghoon Lee</title>
    <link>https://lee2856.github.io/sermonstuff/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sermonstuffs on Seunghoon Lee</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://lee2856.github.io/sermonstuff/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Living</title>
      <link>https://lee2856.github.io/sermonstuff/082822/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lee2856.github.io/sermonstuff/082822/</guid>
      <description>August 28, 2022 Kingdom Living Part 1: Listening to Jesus 3 Blessed are the poor in spirit, for theirs is the kingdom of heaven. 4 Blessed are those who mourn, for they shall be comforted. (Matthew 5:3-4)
Identity shift means repentance. Your reaction &amp;ldquo;comes from&amp;rdquo; who you are.
(v.3) Spiritual poverty implies total inability which needs God&amp;rsquo;s charity (cf. Luke 18:10-14).
Look upward, not inward.
Where is your heart? Do you tolerate your spiritual pride rather than pursue humility?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Living</title>
      <link>https://lee2856.github.io/sermonstuff/090422/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lee2856.github.io/sermonstuff/090422/</guid>
      <description>September 4, 2022 Kingdom Living Part 2: Listening to Jesus 5 Blessed are the meek, for they shall inherit the earth. 6 Blessed are those who hunger and thirst for righteousness, for they shall be satisfied. (Matthew 5:5-6)
(v.5) There is an upside-down paradox &amp;ndash; it does not look blessing for us.
The word &amp;ldquo;meek&amp;rdquo; does not mean &amp;lsquo;weak/shy/coward&amp;rsquo; but mean &amp;lsquo;gentle/humble&amp;rsquo; (strength that accommodates others&amp;rsquo; weakness).
&amp;ldquo;Brothers, if anyone is caught in any transgression, you who are spiritual should restore him in a spirit of gentleness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Living</title>
      <link>https://lee2856.github.io/sermonstuff/091122/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lee2856.github.io/sermonstuff/091122/</guid>
      <description>September 11, 2022 Kingdom Living Part 3: Listening to Jesus 7 Blessed are the merciful, for they shall receive mercy. 8 Blessed are the pure in heart, for they shall see God. (Matthew 5:7-8)
Life is not just primarily about you at all. This seems so countercultural!
Put yourself LAST if you want to live a full life. No.1: Lord, No.2: Others, and No.3: You. Gospel humility is seeking to love God and others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kingdom Living</title>
      <link>https://lee2856.github.io/sermonstuff/091822/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://lee2856.github.io/sermonstuff/091822/</guid>
      <description>September 18, 2022 Kingdom Living Part 4: Listening to Jesus 9 “Blessed are the peacemakers, for they shall be called sons of God. 10 “Blessed are those who are persecuted for righteousness’ sake, for theirs is the kingdom of heaven. 11 “Blessed are you when others revile you and persecute you and utter all kinds of evil against you falsely on my account. 12 Rejoice and be glad, for your reward is great in heaven, for so they persecuted the prophets who were before you.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>